

EMRE ERGÜN SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+905365299933
pvt.emreergun@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/ergunemre
github.com/emre-ergun
Portfolio

SUMMARY

After 10+ years of working on low-level software development, I have moved into web and mobile application development, focusing on modern frameworks like React, React Native, and Next.js. My experience with embedded systems and industrial automation gave me strong problem-solving skills and a good understanding of software architecture. Now, I am applying these skills to create dynamic and responsive web and mobile applications that deliver a great user experience.

SKILLS

- React, React Native, Next.js
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- React Context, Zustand, React Query
- Tailwind, Nativewind, Framer Motion
- Vite, Expo, Git, CI/CD
- Python, C/C++, Rust

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Mar 2024 – Present Istanbul, Turkey

EngramSoft

- Developing web and mobile apps using React, Next.js, and React Native.
- Developed my own portfolio website. Check Out
- Applying CI/CD processes into the projects.
- · Focusing on routing and state management

Senior Software Engineer

Jan 2013 – Present Istanbul, Turkey

Tech Companies

- Developing software for embedded platforms.
- Efficiently using C/C++ to develop real-time software applications.
- Taking advantage of using Pyhton for development process, and testing.
- Using CMake for the better structure and functionality

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering | *Electrical and Electronics Engineering* Karadeniz Technical University

October 2007 – December 2012 Trabzon, Turkey